Guide to the Warren Jay Vinton papers, 1932-1969
Vinton, Warren Jay papers, 1932-1969
- Series VIII. Housing Legislation-Files Arranged by year then alphabetically by folder title
  - Wagner Ellenbogen Bill, 1936
    - "Other Housing Bills-1935 and 1936"-Hearings before Senate Committe on Educ. and Labor on Slum and Low-Rent Public Housing, Jan. 24, 1935-June 29, 1936; Bills on housing and allied subjects, Bill HR 4686, Jan. 24, 1935; Bill HR 6239 Feb. 27, 1935; Bill HR 6998, Mar. 25, 1935; Bill S 3355, July 29, 1935; House resolution 395, Jan. 15, 1936; Bill HR 10269, Jan. 15, 1936; Bill HR 10271, Jan. 15, 1936; Bill HR 10386, Jan. 20, 1936; Bill HR 10512, Jan. 2, 1936; Bill HR 10503 Jan. 22, 1936; Bill HR 11368, Feb. 21, 1936; Bill 11563, March 2, 1936 and reports, bill HR 12835, May 22, 1936, Oct. S3247, June 29, 1936; IPA news bulletin suppplement on Housing Act Juen 1936 (Box 6)
    - "P.W.A. Proposals-1936 WEB" [Wagner Ellenbogen Bill]-Draft bill MC, draft bill TS, Feb. 20, 1956, MS outline of Housing Bill, PWA proposal for housing bill eight draft, Feb. 25, 1936, draft bill, Mar. 4, 1936, memorandum from Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works, Jan. 8, 1936-Feb. 20, 1936 (Box 6)
    - No Title [Senate Report]-Housing Act of 1936, 74th Congress, 2nd session; Senate Report, hearings before Senate Committee on Education and Labor (Box 27)
    - "Wagner and Ellenbogen Bill-1935 WEB"-Bill S. 2392 march 13; Bill HR 7399, Apirl 10 and HR 8666, June 25, 1935; Summary of Hearings on the Wagner Housing Bill before the Committee on Eduction and Labor of the U.S. Senate, April 20-29, 1936 (Chicago, National Association of Housing Officials 1936), June 25, 1935-April 29, 1936 (Box 27)
    - "Studies and Computations-1936 (WEB)" [Wagner-Ellenbogen Bill]-Tables comparing annuitites and capital grant calculations on subsidy values, Catherine Bauer's estimate on rental, Vinton's notes on Wager-Ellenbogen bill, chart on financial workings USHA, March 22-April 20, 1936 (Box 6)
  - Wagner-Steagall Bill, 1937
    - "Congressional History-1937 WSB"-Presidential message to House of Representatives, Nov. 29, 1937, remarks by George O'Brien in House of Representatives, list of speeches in Congress on low-cost housing, Feb. 2-Nov. 29, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Drafts of Bill-1937 (Housing) WSB"-Drafts, confidential committee prints, reports, hearing transcripts of Wagner-Steagall housing bill S1865 to authorize public-aided housing bill considered by the Senate 74th Congress, 2nd session and 85th Congress, 1st session, and amended by House; numbered 1-17 in series and annotated according to changes by Vinton, June 1, 1936-Aug. 18, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Housing Legislation Info. Office Re: Wagner Steagall Bill" [penciled label]-Reports, memos, leaflets, broadsides, from American Federation of Housing Authoritites, Housing Legislation Information Service, Labor Housing COnference [duplicates], 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Housing Legislation Prior to 1937 Act"-Proposed amendments by U.S. Building and Loan League, suggested revision by John Ihlder, suggested ammendment by Boris Shiskin and Catherine Bauer, outline for proposed Federal Housing Development Corp., summary by Coleman woodbury, report of American City Planning Institute of American Federation of Housing Authoritites, tables and statement by Vinton, address by President of NY Real Estate Board, April 15-Oct. 8, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Negotiations-1937 WSB"-Memorandum by American Federation of Housing Authorities," Morgenthau program of June 1, 1937," criticisms of Morgenthau plan and others, notes on Treasury negotiations, notes on Vinton's interview with Mrs. Roosevelt, May 19-27, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Notes and Suggestions-1937 (WS)"-Ms notes, report of Public Housing Committee, U.S. Building and Loan League, Mss. account of Wagner Bill meeting Feb. 18, 1937, draft of changes for bill by John Ihlder, memorandum on Bill by Ihlder notes on adminstrative policy, report of special committee of American City Planning Institue, notes on telephone conversation, corres. from National Association Housing Officials, Large Scale Housing Division FHA.. .[correspondence from] Ill. State Housing Board, Henry Churchill, Federation of Architects, Engineers, Technicians and Chemists, Mortion Bodfish, Raymond Unwin, Charles Abrams, Coleman Woodbury etc. samples of forms for grant payments, suggested amendments by Washington Housing Association, clippings, article from Architectural Forum, Jan. 18, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Other Housing Bills-1937" (WSB) [Wagner-Steagall Bill]-Copies of bills in Senate and House of Representatives dealing with Federal Home Loan Bank Act, Reconstruction Finance Corp. Authority, Federal Housing Administration Ellenbogen bill, Steagall bill HR 1544 and 5033, Goldsborough bill, Hancock bill etc., etc. some annotated, Jan. 5-Aug. 20, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "PWA Proposals, 1937 (WSB)" [Wagner Steagall Bill]-Drafts of bill, insertions to bill, press release on PWA support, Jan. 20-April 14, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Senate Committe Hearings-1937 WSB" [Wagner Steagall Bill]-Statement of William Green, pres. of AFL before Senate, press release on PWA support statement of Vinton as chief of research, Division of Suburban Resettlement, revised copy of Vinton's statement, transcript of Vinton's hearing before Senate n.d., Ms notes on Senate hearing, May 11, 1937 and April 14, 1937, bound volume of Senate hearings Apirl 14, 15 and May 11, 1937, April 14-May 11, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Statements and Releases-1937 WSB" [Wagner-Steagall Bill]-Proposed amendments by Senator Walsh, addenda to housing statement, report of Chamber of Commerce of the U.S. revival of residential consturciton, Ms notes, report of Building Trades Committee, AFL convention, Nov. 1936-1937 (Box 5)
    - "Studies and Computations-1937 (WSB)-[Wagner Steagall Bill]-proposed ammendments, report of Public Housing Committee, U.S. Building and Loan League, confidential bulletin of U.S. Building and Loan League, Bulletin of Chamber of Commerce of U.S., Vinton's memorandum on minimum price house report, MS notes and tables on room costs, income groups, rent per room including heat, memo from NYC Housing Authority, notes by Chas. Abrams, letter on repayment of loans, June 15, 1936-Aug. 4, 1937 (Box 5)
    - "Wagner Steagall Bill (Miscellaneous" [pencilled tab]-ms suggestions for hearing April 1937 copies of statements, telegrams, press releases, summaries, letters of support bulletins, pamphlets, critiques of Bill, joint statement by American Federation of Labor Housing Committee, Building Trades Housing Committee and Labor Housing Conference, 1936-1937 (Box 5)
- Series IX. U.S. Housing Amendments
  - 1938
    - House Committee on Banking and Currency Hearing on Amendments to U.S.H. Act 1938, Apirl 28-May 5, 1938, Bill S3911, draft of bill showing propsed additions and deletions Bill H10417, NAHO print of proposed bill and explanations, April 1938 (Box 7)
    - U.S. Housing Act of 1937 as amended.. .1938 Public.. .412 75th congress, 1st session, chapter 896 (Box 27)
  - 1939
    - Congress hearings and reports: Senate: Subcommittee of the Committee on Education and Labor; hearings April 7-8, 1939 to amend the United States Housing Act of 1937. Washington GPO 1939 Senate. Report [to accompany S5911] amending the US Housing act of 1937, May 22, 1939, Washington, GPO 1939; House: Committee on Banking and Currency; Hearings June 26-July 13, 1939 Amendments of 1939 to the US Housing Act. Washington GPO, 1939 Congress hearings and reports: Congress, Temporary National Economic Committee, Hearings June 27-July 14, 1939, Investigation of Concertration of Economic Power, Part II Construction Industry, Washington, GPO, 1940; House, Report [to accompany S. 591] July 18, 1939 Amending the US Housing Act of 1937, Washington GPO 1939, April 7-July 18, 1939 (Box 6)
    - "Amendments of 1939-Promotion Material"-"What are Housing Costs" file of charts, tables, etc., leaflets on USHA costs from American Federation of Housing Authorities; acts S. 1275, S. 2240; US Housing Act of 1937 as amended (Dept. of Interior print); USHA memoranda (Box 6)
    - "Debate on S. 591"-Congressional Record, house: Aug. 3, 1939-March. 16, 1939; Senate: June 7, 1939 debate on amendments to USHA Act (Box 7)
    - "House Hearing"-U.S. Housing Act Amendment, 1939; Speech and exhibits presented by Nathan Straus, administrator USHA to House Committee on Banking and Currency, to urge adoption Houisng Bill S. 591, press release on speech MC, June 26, 1939 (Box 7)
    - "Housing Investigation"-U.S. Housing Act Amendment 1939; Resolution to empower Special Senate Committee chosen from Senate Committee on Banking and Currency and on Education and Labor to investigate housing situation TS, MS notes (Box 6)
    - "Studies for 1939 Amendments"-U.S. Housing Act Amendment, 1939; Letter, report to Secretary of Interior for approval of Bureau of Budget, Dept. of Treasury for Housing Bill S.591; charts, calculations on costs of program (TS and MS), administrator's statement to Senate Committee, reply of Treasury Dept., Feb. 8-July 31, 1939 (Box 7)
    - "Tyding's Speech"-U.S. Housing Act Amendment, 1939; Speech of Senator Millard Tydings (D, Me.) attacking USHA program for cost of housing units exemption from local taxation, rent subsitdies on March 8, 1939, Congressional Record, draft of Senator Wagner's reply in Congressional Record, March 16, 1939; MS calculations on costs and Tydings questions extra edition, copy of Natna Straus' answers to questions in Tydings letters of March 31 and April 3, March 8-April 12, 1939 (Box 7)
    - U.S. Congress, House, Report 1208-U.S. Housing Act Amendment, 1939; Amending the U.S. Housing Act of 1937 S. 591, Steagall Report, 76th Congress 1st session Rep. #1208 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Congress, House, Committee on Banking and Currency; Amendments of 1939 to the U.S. Housing Act, Hearings on S. 591, congress 76th, 1st session, June 26-30, July 3-13, 1939 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Congress, Senate-Amending, U.S. Housing Act of 1937, Report 463, S. 591, 76th Congress, 1st session, Sub. Sen. Ellender, May 22, 1939 (Box 21)
    - U.S. Congress, Senate, Committee on Education and Labor; To Amend the U.S. Housing Act of 1937, Hearings on S. 591, 76th Congress, 1st session, April 7, 8, 1939 (Box 21)
    - "United States Housing Act Amendments of 1939, List of material related thereto"-Date prepared by USHA, indexed and tabulated, for department heads and personnel to answer objections to program, copy of memo transmitting folio by Leon Keyserling, Deputy Administrator, Aug. 28, 1939 (Box 7)
  - 1940
    - "Amendments of 1940-Extra Copies"-Proposed amendments of 1940 to U.S. Housing Act of 1937, incl. Bill S. 591 and amendments by House Committee on Banking and Currency; National Defense Housing amendment and other material on defense housing, proposed amendments of 1941, and Senate; Temporary National Economic Committee; Monograph #8 Toward More Housing, April 3, 1940-April 1941 (Box 6)
    - "Amortization Tables-1940 Amend."-Tables on costs of USHA program based on differing amounts of grants and differing length of loans (MC and MS), March-April, 1940 (Box 6)
    - "Capital Grant Plan (100% and 40%)"-Reports and tables on Comparions of Congressman Gores' and 1005 captial grant scheme with USHA plan (TS and MS), Nov. 28, 1939-Feb. 26, 1940 (Box 7)
    - "Interest-Waiver Plan"-Reports, drafts, correspondence, calculations analysis by Vinton on Congressman Gore's "Interest-waiver plan" proposal to abolish annual contributory systema and substitute plan whereby Federal government would lend money to local housing authoritites for a 20-25 year period and waive interest and comparision with current USHA plan, Feb. 26-Aug. 20, 1940 (Box 6)
    - "Proposed amendments"-clipped folder on amendments of 1940 indexed: acts and bills, Bill as reported by House; very short bills 6/8, 6/19; short bill of 6/3/40; long bill of 5/29/40; statements and studies, April 17-June 20, 1940 (Box 6)
    - "Proposed Amend.- S. 434 and H.R. 10416 and 10417"-Bills S. 4344, H.R. 10416, H.R. 10417 and Congressional Record, Sept. 12, 1940, Aug. 27-Sept. 12, 1940 (Box 6)
    - "Studies-1940 Amend."-U.s. Housing Act Amendment, 1940: Statistical data on changed and enlarged USHA program resulting from amendment to Housing Act: reports, correspondence, tables, etc. (MC, TS and MS), Nov. 29, 1949-Oct. 10, 1940 (Box 6)
- Series X. Wagner, Ellender, Taft Bill, 1945-1946
  - [FPHA Testimony on S. 1592]-Statement and graphic material used in support of statement by David Krooth, Acting Commissioner, Federal Public Housing Authority, different versions, some marked "not used", May-July 26, 1946 (Box 8)
  - General Housing Bill S. 1592: Remarks of its sponsors, Nov. 14, 1945, statements by Philip Klutznick before Senate Banking and Currency Committee and Senate Subcommittee on Housing and Urban Redevelopment Housing hearings of Housing Stabilization Act 1945-1946 (Box 27)
  - "Legislation-1946"-Senate report #1131 on General Housing Act of 1946 (s. 1592), National Housing Agency summary on General Housing Act Vinton's "working copy "Committee print of S. 1592, proposed amendments to S. 1592, April 16-Nov. 1946 (Box 27)
  - "S. 1592-1945"-National Home and Property Owners' Foundation statement, pamphlet, brochure opposing Bills 1592, esp. veteran's housing aspect, correspondence to Congressmen from FPNA concerning Bill S. 1592, data, background information etc. speech on Sen. Jesse Wolcott in congressional Reocrd, March 4, 147; Prints of General Housing Act of 1945, S. 1592 (formerly S. 1442) including confidential committee prints and amended versions, July-November 1945; drafts (TS and MC) of S. 1592 and revisions esp. Title III on slum clearance, July 1945-July 26, 1947 (Box 8)
  - "S. 1592 Senate Hearings Nov. 1945" [General Housing Act]-Statement and graphic material by David Krooth Commissioner, FPHA before Senate Committee on Banking Nov. 1945; copy of graphic material for Krooth interleaved with MS, calculations, charts, statistics etc. prepared by project and chart Sept. 1945, photos of slum dwellings and replacements, NHA press release on Philip Klutznick's testimony on requests for public housing and summaries of statements by Klutznick and Administrator Blandfored before Senate Committee on Banking, pamphlets in defense of bill by Wagner, Ellender etc., 4 vols. U.S. Senate Committee on Banking and Currency; Hearings.. .General Housing Act of 1945 Part I, Nov. 27, 1945, unrevised, Part I, Nov.-Dec. 1945 revised; Part II, Dec. 1945-Jan. 1946 revised; Part III [sic] Nov. 28-29, 1945, unrevised, Aug. 27, 1945-Jan. 25, 1946 (Box 8)
  - "S. 1592-1946 General Housing Bill"-Summary of S. 1592, General Housing Bill, President's statement and resignation of Wilson Wyatt, National Housing Expediter, memo from Vinton with correction for Wyatt's testimony; statement by David Krooth before House Banking and Currency Committee and summary; statement by William. Wyatt before House Banking and Currency Committee, copy of letter by Krooth to Rep. Jesse Wolcott July 27; letter D. Krooth to Rep. Jesse Wolcott, Aug. 9, 1946; A.F.L. borchure on General Housing Bill; plus Committee brochure on: Library of Congress Legislative Reference Service; General Housing Bill, Arguments for and against.. .for use of [Senate] Committee on Banking and Currency. Washington, GPO, 1947; memo from Krooth to Commissioner DS Myer on Vinton's work on local participation; National Public Housing Conference's Answer to the Opposition to Public Housing Provisions of S. 1592 and Facts about the Wagner-Ellender-Taft Bill, copies of S. 1592 in Senate, S. 1592 in House and report #1131 by Senator Wagner, April 15-Dec. 14, 1946 (Box 7)
  - "S. 1592" [2nd file]-Drafts of new charts and tables for House Hearings on S. 1592, Leon Keyserling's report on S. 1592, comparison of S. 1592 and H.R. 6205 (Wolcott Bill); memo from L.N. Bloomberg, Assoc. Chief Economist on interpretation of statistics, suggestions for revision of manual, borchures on S. 1592; 2 files with papers clipped indexed and tabulated and labeled materials on S. 1592 (a) 4/1/46 General Materials and Speeches TS (b) Reports and Summaries MC, Jan. 30, 1946 (Box 7)
- Series XI. Wagner, Ellender, Taft Housing Act, 1947-1948
  - "Analysis of Bill" [S. 866]-Analyses of S. 866 numbered 1-5 including amendments by Senators McCarty and Flanders (printed and TS), Feb. 27-June 11, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "Congressional Debate on S. 866-1948"-Congressional Record, House and Senate, covering debate on S. 866, General Housing Act, April 14-July 27, 1948. In binder, indexed by date (Box 9)
  - "S. 866 (1948)-Drafts"-Drafts (TS and MC and printed) numbered #1-10 in binder annotated, some marked "master copy," changes and inserts shown, 2 committee prints of committee amendments (annotated with analysis) proposed by Committee on Banking and Currency (oversize, numbered 10), Feb. 14-April 26, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "P. Glick's Legislative Proposals"-Memoranda from Philip Glick, General Counsel, Public Housing Authority on suggested revisions for S. 866 (General Housing Act 1948) including draft for urban and rural housing act, compromise amendments etc.; #1-6, Aug. 8-Dec. 12, 1947 (Box 9)
  - "House Hearing"-Reports to Raymond Foley, Administrator of Housing and Home Finance, by N.S. Keith on testimony on Bll S. 866 before House Committee on Banking and Currency by favourable and unfavourable witnesses (TS), May 10-June 8, 1948 (Box 9)
  - Housing Act of 1948-Statements for Hearings in House on S. 866, 1948, of W.J. Vinton; items #1-51 (Box 22?)
  - "Housing Act of 1948 (P.L. 901)"-H.R. 6841 (Wolcott Bill); H.R. 6888 (Wolcott Bill) and accompanying House report, covering letters, letter from Bernard Grove (Acting Counsel) on mortgage insurance extract from Washington Post and Congressional Record, H.R. 6959 and House Joint Resolution 445 as passed both Houses, summary of Housing Act, sttement by Pres. criticizing failure of H.R. 6959 to provide for low-rent public housing, slum clearance and urban redevelopment, Aug. 5-12, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "PL 301 (McCarthy Act)-1947" [Amendment to Houisng Act]-Bill S. 1361 (to amend Housing Act 1937) in Senate and house, Senate and House report, notes on testimony before House Committee on Banking and Currency on S. 1361, memoranda to Raymond Foley, Dillon Myer, proposed amendment, MS calculations; "Also see folder Reactiviation under 'Projects, Deferred'", May 28-July 25, 1947 (Box 10)
  - "Miscellaneous" [S. 866]-Correspondence and drafts concerning farm and rural housing; meoranda on data needed for hearings, Puerto Rico projects, revisions of Bill S. 866 mainly from Philip Glick, General Counsel; minutes of Legislative Committee meeting, National Public Housing Conference statement by Dillon Myer, Commissioner, FPHA, Sept. 11, 1946-May 21, 1947 (Box 10)
  - "Miscellaneous, S. 866-1948"-Schedule of hearings May 1948, history of Taft-Ellender-Wagner Bill and substitute housing measures, memoranda, reprint from Pittsburgh Courier, extracts from Congressional Record, record of voting, special section of The Nation, May 1948 on housing, speech prepared by L.N. Bloomberg, Nov. 3, 1947-June 18, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "S. 866-1947"-[National Housing Commission]-Binder of indexed materials on National Housing Commission]-Binder of indexed material on National Housing Commission Act including statements, summary, analysis etc., Senate Committee on Banking and Currency hearing, Committee print on Housing Act of 1937 as amended by S. 866, Senate Committee on Housing and Banking report on S. 866, March 18-April 24, 1947 (Box 10)
  - "Public Housing and Slum Clearance-Misc. 1947"-Bills and resolutions on various aspects: S. 701, S. 1202 and covering letter; S. 1293, S. 1596, S. 1597; HR 2025 and covering letter, HR 4012 and covering letter, HR 4144; House resolutions 168, 237 and House joint resolutions 206, Feb. 24-July 10, 1947 (Box 10)
  - "S. 866-Releases"-clippings, press release, Monthly Business Review, Feb. 1, 1947, v. 29, #2, U.S. Conference of Mayor's "America Can Not Afford Slums," "Questions and Answers about S. 866" (Box 10)
  - "Senate Hearings (on S. 866)"-Recording of voting in Senate on housing bill and amendments, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "Similar Bills" [S. 866-1948]-4 bills on housing, S. 2317 introduced by Sen. McCarthy, HR 5726 introduced by Rep. Buchannan, HR 5862 introduced by Rep. Fletcher and HR 5920 introduced by Rep. Boggs, March 5-22, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "Speeches-House" [S. 866-1948]-Speeches prepared by L. Bloomberg (Information Division) for Wheaton, L. Johnson for various southern cities and on varied topiecs, exerpts from Congressional Record (TS), June 1948 (Box 9)
  - "Statements" [S. 866-1948]-Statements on amendments and revisions proposed for Housing Act, on policy; examples of project financing, costs, annual contributions; answers and exhibits prepared to be used by senators for questions in House Debates, hearings, Democratic National Committee newspapers; chiefly by Vinton, A.R. Miller and anon, March 31-July 22, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "S. 866-1948"-Amendments to S. 866 of March 15 1948 (Flanders amendments) and April 13, 1948 (McCarthy amendments); 2. 866 in the House of Rep. April 26, 1948; Committee [on Banking and Currency] print March 31, 1948; arguments against McCarthy amendment by [NPHC]; MC letter to Senate by Sen. McCarthy; hearings before Senate Committee on Banking and Currency amendments to S. 866 March 14, April 1, 1948, supplemental report from Senate Banking and Currency Committee to accompany S. 866, March 15-April 26, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "Testimony of Mr. Egan in House"-Statement of John Taylor Egan, Public Housing Commissioner before House of Rep. Committee on Banking and Currency, May 3; testimony of Egan before Committee May 5 with corrections and inserts; statements and tables (PC) prepared for insertion in Egan's testimony by Vintona and A.R. Miller, covering letters, May 3-June 4, 1948 (Box 9)
  - "Testimony of Opponents"-[on Bill S. 866] Testimony before House Committee on Banking and Currency, June 1948 by National Association of Real Estate Boards; Testimony before Senate Committee on Bank and Currency April and May 1947 by National Association of Home Builders, Building Products Institute, National Association of Real Estate Boards, National Association of Home Builders, National Home and Property Owners Foundation; Chamber of Commerce of the U.S. Mortgage Bankers' Association of America, Commerce and Industry Assoc. of NY and National Savings and Loan League (MC), March 18, 1947-June 7, 1948 (Box 10)
  - Testimony of Others [S. 866-1948]-Testimony before House Committee on Banking and Currency by government and private witnesses (MC) (Box 9)
  - "Testimony of Proponents" [to Bill S. 866]-Testimony before Senate Committee on Banking and Currency, March; by U.S. Conference of Mayors, National Public Housing Conference, National Assoc. of Housing Officials, American Assoc. of Social Workers et. al., American Veterans Committee, CIO nd AFL statement on behalf of Mayor O'Dwyer of NY Federal Home Loan Bank Administrator, Raymond Foley, NHA administrator and Charles Brannan, Asst. Sec. Agriculture, March 18-20, 1947 (Box 10)
  - U.S. Housing Act of 1937 as it would be amended by s. 866 (General Housing Act) 80th Congress, 2nd session committee prints: annotated with explanation April 1948 (2 copies); Annotated with section analysis April 1948; bill HR 6888 June; Senate Committee on Banking and Currency Supplemental Report (Box 27)
- Series XII. U.S. Congress Joint Committee on Housing, 1947-1948